tweetangels.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy - tweetangels.com

Company values and respects the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains the ways in which Company collects, stores, processes and uses personal information when you access or use the Service. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.  
This Privacy Policy was last changed on 

When you use the Service, Company’s systems and administrators may collect various types of personal information to enable Company to provide the Service, as well as certain features of the Service or interaction with third-parties or Third-Party Services.

Company may collect non-personally-identifying information, such as browser types, language preferences, referring sites, date and time of visitor requests, server information, usage metrics, previous activities and duration of sessions, to better understand how the Service is being used and deliver reliable and enhanced functionality.

Company may collect potentially personally-identifying information, such as Internet Protocol addresses, media access control addresses, network routes, technical data, user and usage statistics, traffic patterns and popularity of information shared via the Service, to better understand how the Service is being used.

Company may collect personally-identifying information, such as names, addresses, email addresses, telephone numbers, payment information and verified identity data to implement specific features or functions. The exact nature and type of personally-identifying information collected will vary according to the feature, such as providing contact details to create a verified account, if applicable.

Company uses both non-personally-identifying information and potentially personally-identifying information to enhance functionality of the Service, resolve technical errors, provide you with the correct and most up to date version of the Service and to improve the overall accessibility of the Service.  
Please note that any information you submit to forums, message boards or Third-Party Services may be publicly viewable. In such event, any privacy rights you may have concerning the submitted information will be released. Public disclosure of information via such methods may also cause you to receive unwanted communications.

Company will only disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to those officers, directors, employees, agents or contractors that have a legitimate need to know such information. In such cases, those officers, directors, employees, agents or contractors to whom potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information is disclosed will have signed a non-disclosure agreement with Company prohibiting any unauthorized disclosure.

Company may release aggregated forms of non-personally-identifying information and technical data to third-parties for informational or research purposes. However, Company will not disclose personally-identifying information without your explicit consent, except to the extent legally required or necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims and process, in the event of an emergency pertaining to your health or safety, if you violate Company’s Terms of Service or compelled to do so by court order or applicable law

Company has taken commercially reasonable technical and organizational security measures against loss or unauthorized processing of potentially personally-identifying or personally-identifying information, including without limitation, the use of encryption, firewalls and Secure Sockets Layer and Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard protocols. Additionally, Company implements general industry security standards as well as physical safeguards of the locations where such information is stored.

When you provide Company with potentially personally-identifying or personally-identifying information, you consent to Company’s collection of such information and explicitly authorize Company to use it to provide the Service for you access or use.

In the event that Company’s officers, directors, employees, agents or contractors are accessing potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information from a remote location, you consent to the transfer of such information to the remote location for processing.

You also consent to the disclosure of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to Company’s parent company, subsidiaries, acquirers of Company’s assets or a successors by merger.  
You may withdraw your consent at any time by notifying Company via email at [support@tweetangles.com](mailto:%20support@tweetangles.com)

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California may obtain certain information about the types of personal information that companies with whom they have an established business relationship have shared with third-parties during the preceding calendar year. The law provides that companies must inform consumers about the categories of personal information that have been shared with third-parties, the names and addresses of those third-parties and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third-parties. To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by Company pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact Company via email at [support@tweetangles.com](mailto:%20support@tweetangles.com)

Despite Company’s commercially reasonable efforts to protect potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information, no security measure is impenetrable. Company cannot guarantee the security of Company’s software, systems, websites or platforms, nor can Company guarantee that potentially personally-identifying or personally-identifying information will not be intercepted during transmission. Any communication of potentially personally-identifying or personally-identifying information by you to the Service is at your own risk.

As part of the functionality of the Service, you may be able access or use Third-Party Services. The security and safety of any potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information or other data you transmit to Third-Party Services is beyond Company’s control or responsibility. Company cannot and will not be liable for any potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information or other data you transmit to any Third-Party Service.

Company may use Third-Party Services to analyze, measure or otherwise process potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. The specific processing of analytics is subject to the respective Third-Party Service’s Privacy Policy.

Whenever potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information is transmitted to or processed by a Third-Party Service, such information is no longer governed by Company’s Privacy Policy and Terms of Service Agreement. Third-Party Services have their own Privacy Polices, security measures and procedures and Company assumes no liability to investigate, assess, approve or monitor such protocols. Company strongly recommends that you review the respective Third-Party Service privacy policy so you can understand the method and manner in which your potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information will be collected, stored, processed and used when transmitted to or processed by any Third-Party Service.

If you live outside the United States, any information you provide to the Service will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By using the Service, you are transferring information to the United States for collection, storage, processing and use and you expressly consent to such use. You are solely and exclusively responsible for compliance with your jurisdiction. Your information will never be treated with a degree of care less than that stated in this Privacy Policy.

Like many other Internet services, the Service may use cookies. A cookie is a small amount of information stored locally on your computer or device that enables the Service to recall certain data or settings. Company uses cookies to enable tracking and analysis of usage patterns, sections and sites visited prior to, during and after accessing the Service. If you do not wish to have cookies stored on your computer or device, you should immediately change your settings to disable or refuse the use of cookies before using the Service.  
The following is a non-exclusive list of cookies that Company may store on your computer or device when you access or use the Service:

\\_session\\_id: unique token, sessional, allows storage of information about your session

\\_secure\\_session\\_id: unique token, sessional  
PREF: persistent for a very short period

**Insert Other Cookies Used**

If you disable or refuse the use of cookies, certain features of the Service may not function properly, fully or as advertised.

The Service is not available for access or use by individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. Company does not knowingly collect potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information from anyone under eighteen (18) years of age. If Company discovers the unknowing collection of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information from someone under eighteen (18) years of age, Company will delete the collected information immediately upon discovery. By accessing and using the Service, you represent and warrant that you are at least eighteen (18) years of age.

Company may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in information practices. Any changes will take effect immediately upon their publication via the Service. Company encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Policy for the latest information and updates.

If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information you have transmitted to Company, register a complaint or need additional information, please contact Company via email at [support@tweetangles.com](mailto:support@tweetangles.com)
